https://www.twifordlaw.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Twiford Law Firm, P.C. (“we”). This privacy policy is intended both to: 1) describe how our website may collect and use information from your Internet enabled device (i.e. your computer, tablet, smartphone or other device — and browsers or apps used to access the Internet), and 2) describe how you may opt out of any such collection and use. Please contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.Data collection and cookies. Features or partners of our website may collect data including, but not limited to: the number of visitors to our site, the time spent on our site and pages clicked, the types of devices used to access our site, and the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors. We use this information to improve our website and marketing. This data is collected by sending cookies (or similar tracking technology) to your device. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; if you previously provided personally identifiable information, however, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties; and this privacy policy does not cover third parties’ use of cookies. You may configure your device to limit or prevent access by cookies, such as to notify you when you receive a cookie, to block all cookies, or to delete existing cookies.Partners and features that collect information. Our website marketing partners or features that collect data as described above may include, among others, Google Analytics, other analytics programs, and Google AdWords remarketing service. Remarketing involves tracking devices that have visited our website in order to display ads for our services on other websites. Use these links to learn how Google uses data it collects, to prevent Google Analytics from using data from your device, or to opt out of Google’s interest-based ads.Information you send us. Please see our disclaimer, which generally addresses information you intentionally send us using e-mail or any contact form on this website. If you submit your name or contact information to us, we may use it to send you information about our services. You may opt out of receiving further information from us by contacting us or, where applicable, by using an “unsubscribe” option included in our communications. We will not sell or give your personally identifying information to other parties for their own direct advertising purposes.For California residents. As described above, we do not disclose personal information to third parties for their own use in direct marketing. The information above also explains how you may opt out of permitting our website or partners from collecting information from your device.Changes to this policy. We reserve the right to update this policy. If we make updates, we will change the modification date below.Last modified. 8/10/2016
Practice Areas
Civil Litigation
Administrative Law
Criminal Law
Estate Planning
Family & Domestic Law
Governmental Law
Health Care Law
Email me
Call me Details About ProblemWhat County were you charged?Preferred LawyerNew Client - No PreferenceLauren Arizaga-WombleCourtney HullMegan MorganJohn MorrisonEdward O'NealMark WarrenHP Williams Jr.CAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
News
Oct
14
Social Security Disability for Children in 2020
October 14th, 2020
A child under age 18 who has a disability may be able to receive Supplemental Security Income benefits under specific eligibility requirements. The social security disability for children rules are different from SSI eligibility requirements for adul…
Read More
Sep
22
Can You Move Out of State Without a Child Custody Agreement or Modification?
September 22nd, 2020
With the arrival of the Covid-19 pandemic in the spring of 2020, our family law attorneys at The Twiford Law Firm are at the forefront of helping parents face a host of new challenges. A frequent question from our clients is whether a parent can move…
Read More
Two Convenient Locations
Twiford Law Firm, P.C.
203 North Road Street P.O. Box 99
Elizabeth City, NC 27907-0099
Telephone:
(252) 338-4151
Toll Free:
(800) 395-4151
Fax:
(252) 338-8546
Email:
Twiford Law Firm, P.C.
111 Currituck Commercial Drive Suite A P.O. Box 669
Moyock, NC 27958
Telephone:
(252) 435-2811
Toll Free:
(888) 435-2811
Fax:
(252) 435-9974
Email:
© 2020 Twiford Law Firm, P.C. View Our Disclaimer | Privacy Policy Law Firm Website Design by The Modern Firm
Copyright © 2020
Twiford Law Firm, P.C.
COVID-19 ALERT
COVID-19 Quarantine Update
In regards to Covid-19,  We are reviewing the best guidelines for our city and state for how
we should conduct business and plan to update this message as soon as we can.
Please call our office(s) to get learn how we are engaging with current clients and new at this time.
CLOSE
